hello and welcome everyone at the Active
inference Journal we are eagerly seeking
contributors who would like to help
improve the transcripts named entities
list and topics discussed in the ongoing
Chris Fields course physics as
information processing right now it's
May 2023.
if you're already planning to spend time
on this course we hope you'll consider
working with the journal as well this is
a unique opportunity to build editorial
skills and make high leverage open
science contributions to the active
inference ecosystem
specifically this work entails listening
carefully to the course lectures and
discussions and making corrections to
the AI generated transcript for this we
use assembly AI
for example
for the transcript of the first lecture
see this link here
this is what the transcript looks like
on the GitHub we have a markdown file
that allows line by line editing and we
use this markdown file as the basis for
further rendering and translation into
different languages as well as training
on language models and other functions
we're also building out the list of
entities named that is people and topics
so here we have people named and already
from the background video and first
lecture we have dozens of names that
have been mentioned and we have topics
discussed so this will continue to grow
and that will improve the the
scholarship and the relevance of this
work as we know so many of the
interesting topics being mentioned
all the transcripts and materials
related to this course will be published
open source
if you want to see what that looks like
or what that can look like check out the
earlier transcript of the mark Psalms
live streams
where we enrich the transcript with
images and tables of content as well so
this is a really important open science
way to improve the impact of the live
streams and the videos that we have and
it is also really important for
accessibility
we have synchronous meetings for the
active inference journal in the active
inference institute's Discord on Mondays
at 13 UTC although most of the work on
this project is done asynchronously for
example via the GitHub links above
if you're interested in participating in
the journal on this project please let
us know by joining the journal channel
on the Discord or by emailing
activeinference gmail.com Dave what else
would you add to this
working on detailed editing of a
transcript is a great way to learn the
material in depth and particularly to
spot things that you might have thought
you understood that you didn't really
understand
so do it
great great points
totally agree all right so looking
forward to people's participation here
and till the next update thank you